Morgan Devish UX Designer

morgandevishux@gmail.com

(774) 280-6117

Webster, MA

www.behance.net/mdevish52

m www.linkedin.com/in/morgandevish

Profile

UX Designer with the ultimate goal of creating design solutions that cause people to not only love the product they're using, but be inspired by it. A motivated self-starter that has been recognized by past employers for the ability to be flexible while grasping new concepts quickly and with minimal guidance.

Experience

Umass Medical School, Data Operator

May 2018 - Present | Worcester, MA

- Enter, review and sort daily specimen batches for processing with 95% accuracy
- Verify newborn screening information and administer hospital reports with accurate test results

Better Business Bureau, Trade Practices Consultant

July 2016 - May 2018 | Worcester, MA

- Lead role in monitoring business practices in relation to licensing, government actions, website review, patterns of complaints, customer reviews, logo violations and arbitrations
- Strategize with local businesses about improving their website and increasing customer satisfaction

Worcester State University, Spanish Clinic Tutor

September 2015 - May 2016 | Worcester, MA

- Prepare students for written and oral exams
- Increase writing proficiency and assist with research projects

Education

CareerFoundry, Certified UX Design Program

May 2018- Present | Online Certification

- Intensive training program for UX Designers, specializing in UX process and methodology that includes user research, user journeys, user personas, testing, information architecture and visual design fundamentals
- Designed several real world projects using software such as InVision,
 UXPin and Sketch for wireframes and prototypes

CodeAcademy, UI Interfaces Certification

March - April 2018 | Online Certification

Worcester State University, BS Sociology, BA Spanish

September 2012 - May 2016 | Worcester, MA

- Concentration in Global Studies
- 3.9 GPA Achieved Dean's List for 8 semesters

Skills

UX/UI Design
Wireframing
Rapid Prototyping
Web Design
Mobile Design
Color Theory
User Personas
Interaction Design
Usability Testing
User Research
HTML5/CSS3 (basics)

Tools

Sketch InVision UxPin Balsamiq Omnigraffle MS Office Keynote

Awards

Alpha Mu Gamma

The Faith T Zaedey Award for Research and Writing

Academic Major Award in Spanish